[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Shattered Mountain",
        "Description": "Yash Zafar's investigations into Shattered Mountain have uncovered signs that the Corrupted took an unusual interest in finding and imprisoning a specific individual. Search for this mysterious person and determine if they could be an ally in your fight against the Tempest.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should push the advantage.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I was hoping you'd say this, so I took the liberty of ordering scouts to venture closer to the foot of the Shattered Mountain.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll see you on the road to Shattered Mountain.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I did not expect friendly welcome nor Corruption beaten back, but you and your fellow Soulwardens have accomplished much.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Through a Mirror Darkly",
        "Description": "Father Russo is convinced from your account that a spark of goodness still exists within the Tempest. Gather relics saturated with her past emotions from the time before she fell to Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Our minds are bound somehow.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh...? Good Lord… that's the answer! If we can access her thoughts, we can rouse the emotions she tries to suppress!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go quickly. Isabella is on the verge of eternal damnation - and dragging the rest of the world with her.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You have done well. These objects harbor powerful echoes from Isabella's past, when she still had some trace of innocence.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Yash_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Wisdom and Madness and Folly",
        "Description": "With the collection of the relics, Father Russo wishes to psychically attack the Tempest with her own memories and feelings. Join him atop the nearby vista in view of the Tempest's stronghold, and strike back at her with all of your power.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I've blocked her out of my mind.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh… but of course you have. Still, if you're the one who erected these mental barriers, you can surely lower them as well.",
        "InProgressResponse": "She may try to resist, but you alone can reach that goodness which remains. I believe in you, Soulwarden.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The prisoner seems to have captured all your attention since you arrived. Does he have insights related to our strategy here?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Phaeris_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Marched Across the Land",
        "Description": "Now that Isabella has been wounded and frightened, it is time to secure enough allies that can overcome the defenses of Myrkgard. Yash Zafar has heard rumors that Morgaine is in trouble; search Edengrove and bring her back to the safety of the Soulwarden encampment.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need more allies.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Agreed. Sun Fuchun promised she would send aid from Ebonscale, but I also hoped we could re-enlist the Sorceress Morgaine.",
        "InProgressResponse": "It worries me - the Corrupted are aware of our presence, but they do not attack.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Our Blighted brethren and sistren come, but we cannot hear them. Their madness is not like that of the human friend.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Morgaine_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Harvest is Come",
        "Description": "Morgaine has returned to her senses after being helped by the Angry Earth Peacemaker. Phaeris provides a surprising opportunity for the Soulwardens to secure Blighted forces in the upcoming battle against the Tempest. Create a connection between Phaeris and the Blighted Angry Earth so they can communicate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“We'll need allies for the attack.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "We cannot ask Blighted to fight with you, because we cannot hear their song… here, in this place, my song is alone.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Yes, speak to the human friend. She is tired from travels... but her wisdom can aid us, aid the Blighted sistren and brethren.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I cannot believe I'm saying this, but it's actually a relief to be back in human society. No offense to Phaeris, she's quite nice.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Sun_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Angel That Brings Death",
        "Description": "Morgaine is concerned that even with Blighted Angry Earth on their side, the Soulwardens remain at a strategic disadvantage. After being reminded of her ability in Weaver's Fen to command the Lost, she will attempt to exert her will over the Ancient Guardians in the nearby cavern to further bolster your forces.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need more allies.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The city on the mountain is called Myrkgard, as imposing as it is well-protected. It will take some army to breach its defenses.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I have mixed feelings, Soulwarden. If this works, there's an outstanding wager I'll owe my brother.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Greetings, Soulwarden. On behalf of Emperor-in-Waiting Zhou Liang, I have come to offer the Dynasty's assistance to your cause.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "As Black as Sackcloth",
        "Description": "At the behest of Emperor-in-Waiting Zhou Liang, Sun Fuchun has come to Shattered Mountain to offer support. She requires a special ingredient to concoct war-grade smoke bombs that will both distract the Corrupted and prevent reinforcements from flanking the Soulwardens during the imminent assault on Myrkgard.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm happy you'll be joining us.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Good, because I need someone I can depend on. I've got a plan, but I could use some help.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Normally, I'd feel a bit overwhelmed being in such a dark place. Yet, I feel oddly exhilarated and in control.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You are a busy and respected person, I've come to realize. Fortunately, that makes you easier to find… as long as one moves fast!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "To Prepare a Place For You",
        "Description": "After much research, Father Russo has discovered what he believes is the means to achieve the Tempest's defeat and salvation. Search the depths of Illurmin Canyon for two Ancient Artifacts that he requires to craft a powerful spiritual weapon.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"… is there some meaning in that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Don't you see? I've found what we need! Deep in the pits of this scarred canyon are Ancient objects of immense spiritual power.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The end is coming. And our fates… the world's fate... will be decided.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Remarkable. These artifacts are exactly what we needed. I feel as if I have awoken from a nightmare to bask in the morning sun.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Time For Peace, A Time for War",
        "Description": "On the eve of battle, the mood in the Soulwarden War Camp is grim. While Father Russo works to fashion his ultimate weapon, walk the camp and bolster the morale of your many allies.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Let's put your plan to the test.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "And so the ending does finally begin, the conclusion of a long saga that brought us to these shores.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Your pardon. These final steps will take the whole of my concentration. We will speak again shortly.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It is done. A masterwork, had I the luxury of the sin of pride. For your Azoth Staff - a means to achieve Isabella's redemption.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_alt_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Time For Peace, A Time for War",
        "Description": "On the eve of battle, the mood in the Soulwarden War Camp is grim. While Father Russo works to fashion his ultimate weapon, walk the camp and bolster the morale of your many allies.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Let's put your plan to the test.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "And so the ending does finally begin, the conclusion of a long saga that brought us to these shores.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Your pardon. These final steps will take the whole of my concentration. We will speak again shortly.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It is done. A masterwork, had I the luxury of the sin of pride. For your Azoth Staff - a means to achieve Isabella's redemption.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_06",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Walls Came Tumbling Down",
        "Description": "The time has come to strike at the heart of Corruption. As the vanguard of the Soulwardens and their newfound allies, assault Myrkgard and overthrow the Tempest's dominion.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Thank you. I am prepared.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I do not know if one can ever be prepared for something like this. Facing such darkness is beyond mortal comprehension. But…",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will follow wherever you lead, Soulwarden, and say a prayer for the souls of us all.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The evil permeating this blasphemous cathedral has a taste. Only divine judgment can purge its foulness from existence.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99G_Grace_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Prodigal Daughter",
        "Description": "The Tempest has been backed into a corner and has nowhere to retreat now except for within herself. Before she is able to open more Corruption Portals throughout Aeternum, use Father Russo's weapon to enter her mind and face her in combat for the last time.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's she doing?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That is how I found her… secure within the depths of her own mind, commanding Corruption by thought alone.",
        "InProgressResponse": "\"If I shall go and prepare a place for you, I will come again and will take you to myself: that where I am, you also may be.\"",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "A bit disappointed I couldn't land the last blow. But in a manner of thinking… maybe I did!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The First Things Have Passed Away",
        "Description": "Corruption has been weakened and its loudest voice has been silenced: the Tempest is gone. Find Father Russo to understand what will become of Aeternum in the passing of this storm, and celebrate the victory with your allies.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm happy you came back, Grace.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Bah! What choice did you leave me with? It's been a lifetime since we met on that beach; I couldn't just sail away.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Off with you now! Don't worry, your Grace will be sticking around. That's a promise, that is!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You made it!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
